independentlivingbullion.com 2014-07-11

# Privacy Policy - Independent Living Bullion

Independent Living Bullion (“ILB”) values your privacy, and as a result we collect the minimum information on our visitors that allows us to provide you with the best possible service. This Policy describes the manner in and extent to which we collect and use your personal information online.

###  ** _What We Collect from the User and How We Use It_**

During general visits to the site, ILB collects generic information about our visitors like pages browsed, web browser used, and other general usage information using Google Analytics. At no time is this linked to you personally. This general information helps ILB improve its Website and services and give you the best online experience.

Only during registration and site inquiries – in which we require email address and other pertinent personal information – is such information collected, and only with your permission, which is given as part of the registration process. Email addresses and other personal information collected is used for delivery of specific promotions and/or site inquiry. In addition, any email address collected during registration may be used to deliver advertising, promotional material, and helpful insights into the precious metals industry directly from ILB.You may opt out of receiving such material at any time.

###  ** _No Disclosure to Third Parties_**

ILB will never share your personal information, including your email address, with any other third party without your consent, except as may be required by law. Such a situation might include disclosing user information to appropriate authorities, whether by subpoena or other legitimate legal request, or to protect the legal interests of ILB. To modify the limited customer data we have collected or if you wish to “opt-out” of any free content or marketing you have received, simply please click the unsubscribe button on our email or contact us toll free at 1-800-800-1865.

###  ** _Children and Privacy_**

ILB’s Website is not intended for the use of children under thirteen years old nor is it directed to children under the age of thirteen. In compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), we do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen through the Website or otherwise. If we learn that any user is under thirteen or that we have inadvertently received personally identifiable information from such a user, we will remove that user’s information from our database. If you become aware that your child has registered with our Website, contact us at 1-800-800-1865 or through our [online form](https://www.independentlivingbullion.com/contact), and we will remove your child’s information from our database.
